# David Conner

I am a digital media graduate (M.Sc.) with project experience in educational research as well as in the private sector. During my studies I focused on e-assessment software and moved over to b2b software for IBM Notes Domino.

> Status: Fullstack JS Engineer, M.Sc. Digital Media,

Consultant

> Fields: Project Management, Software Development,

Consulting

# **Education**

Virginia Western Community College

## 2021 - 2023; 2006 - 2008

## Mechatronics Systems E.T.

- ▶ Master Thesis: Semi Automated Scoring in Technology Based Assessment
- Developed and evaluated an algorithm for semi automated scoring of spreadsheet data

Virginia Tech

## 2004-2006 Computer Science

- ➤ Co-Invented a touch table application for medical support, co-developed software (Java)
- Formed a scrum team, mainted project dev server (Debian), surveyed target audience

## **Education**

University of Bremen

# 2012 - 2015

# **Master Studies Digital Media**

- Inter-cultural classes in English, covering special topics in computer science and design
- Professionalized in research methods, software development and e-assessment

University of Melbourne

## 2009 - 2010 Semester Abroad

- Mastered six months of study and trans-cultural experience in Melbourne, Australia
- ▶ Finished machine programming, information visualization, professional essay writing

University of Bremen

# 2007 - 2012

## **Bachelor Studies Digital Media**

- ▶ Fundamentals in Computer Science
- ▶ Bachelor thesis focused on experimental redesign of the keyboard to support functional illiterates.

## **Summary**

I am a digital media graduate (M.Sc.) with project experience in educational research as well as in the private sector. During my studies I focused on e-assessment software and moved over to b2b software for IBM Notes Domino. Currently I develop and evaluate the next generation learning management system with Meteor based on an extensive nursing curriculum for healthcare education. I also love fitness, martial arts, videogames, news and Sci-Fi series.

> Tech: Meteor, Javascript, Bootstrap, Mongodb, Git,

Webstorm, Sourcetree, Terminal

▶ Loves: Global Game Jam, Sci-Fi series, Stackover-

flow, Fitness and Martial Arts

# **Experience**

Virginia Western Community College

## 2022 - 2023

## **Engineering Student Aide**

- Maintain Ender-3 Pro and Raise3D printers. Synced Ender-3 configurations for PLA plastics
- ➤ Created an Autodesk Fusion CNC config for a Velocity CNC. Collected notes on almost all equipment including support links and digital copies of manuals

## RAKE Digital

#### 2018

**Cloud Engineer** 

- ▶ Used MS SQL table metadata to quickly learn the accounting database schema for Millennium and ReadyPay
- Designed an application stack with LoopbackJS and Angular 6 to automate payroll tasks in Azure

Voxxel (Startup)

#### 2015 - 2017

Founder

- Built a Rails API to back prototypes in iOS, Android and AngularJS (with Web Audio)
- Voxxel enabled fans to score their impersionations of movie quotes and accents

#### Oscil8 (Startup)

## 2011 - 2015

Founder

- Oscil8 was designed to be the "Github for Music Producers"
- Developed a business model and strategic vision

## Left + Right (Contract)

## 2014

## **Student Assistant / Programmer**

- Developed a web service to extend a Ruby on Rails application with reporting on SQL Views
- ➤ Cached report results in MongoDB to enable a dashboard

# Jumpcloud

## 2013

## Student Assistant / Programmer

- > Full stack development using a NodeJS API and MongoDB
- ▶ Integration tests using Mocha, Selenium and Soda